虚幻勇士冒险 S2E1 Anthea 由özberk özen制作
视频来源：https://youtu.be/6_uFIw6DIFE，中文字幕由熙洛Chincode制作，翻译：jky，Albeta
[Music]
[音乐]
Look at this photo honey.
看看这张照片 亲爱的
It's so beautiful.
它是如此美丽
What makes the picture so beautiful.
是什么让这张照片如此美丽
Well, you are a myth.
恩 你是一个神话
You silly.
别说傻话了
I love you so much.
我非常爱你
I love you too honey.
我也爱你 亲爱的
Which name should we give to our daughter.
我们应该给我们的女儿取什么名字
I have the perfect name for her, Aelita.
我有一个完美的名字 Aelita
Oh my God look at her Waldo.
哦 我的天哪 看看她 Waldo
She's so so beautiful.
她真是太漂亮了
Well she is just like you.
恩 她就像你一样
She will be a princess when she grows up.
她长大后会成为一个公主
She will have the perfect life.
她会有完美的生活
[Music]
[音乐]
Aelita just fell asleep and the terrible snowstorm just started.
Aelita刚刚睡着 而可怕的暴风雪刚刚开始
What are you working on, dear?
你在做什么 亲爱的？
I just bought an old factory in France.
我刚刚在法国买了一个旧工厂
Oh sounds great but why.
哦 听起来不错 但为什么呢？
To invest in our daughter's future.
为了给我们女儿的未来投资
[Music]
[音乐]
Waldo please tell me this isn't about project Carthage.
Waldo 请告诉我这不是有关迦太基项目的
Waldo don't you there.
Waldo 你不要去那里
You know they are dangerous.
你知道他们很危险
You saw everything with your own eyes.
你亲眼看到了一切
Please. Please you have to promise me to stay away from them.
求你了 求你了 你得答应我离他们远一点
Please.
求你了
I know how dangerous they are.
我知道他们有多危险
I won't get near them.
我不会靠近他们的
There is no need to worry about that.
没有必要担心这个问题
Please calm down.
请冷静下来
I am so tired.
我太累了
Let's let's get to sleep.
让我们去睡觉吧
[Music]
[音乐]
Aelita's so sleepy
Aelita很困了
and I will go to the village to send the rest of the papers.
而我要去村里把剩下的文件送走
What about breakfast?
早餐怎么办？
I will have it when I get back home.
我回家后会吃的
Bye. I love you.
再见 我爱你们
Be careful out there.
在外面要小心
[Music]
[音乐]
Come. Come to mommy.
来吧 到妈妈这里来
Oh you made it sweet heart.
哦 你成功了 亲爱的
[Music]
[音乐]
Okay now smile to the camera.
好了 现在对着镜头微笑
[Music]
[音乐]
And this ship crossed all the stormy oceans.
这艘船渡过了所有刮着暴风雨的海洋
This ship was called Skidbladnir.
这艘船被称为Skidbladnir
[Music]
[音乐]
Oh oh he's so cute.
哦 哦 他是如此可爱
How should I call him.
我应该怎么称呼他
What about Mr. Puck?
帕克先生怎么样？
It means elf.
它的意思是精灵
Do you like it?
你喜欢它吗？
Oh thank you mommy.
哦 谢谢你 妈妈
I love you mommy.
我爱你 妈妈
I love you daddy.
我爱你爸爸
It's like maths.
这就像数学
Let me show you.
让我给你看
Twinkle twinkle little star.
一闪一闪亮晶晶
How I wonder what you are.
满天都是小星星
[Music]
[音乐]
What are we going Daddy?
我们要去哪里 爸爸？
Well we're going to the frozen lake.
恩 我们要去冰湖
Wow but why are we going there?
哇 但我们为什么要去那里？
Because today we will skate.
因为今天我们要滑冰
What but I don't know how to skate.
什么 但我不知道如何滑冰
And that's exactly why we are here.
而这正是我们来这里的原因
Aelita, darling slow down wait a second.
Aelita 亲爱的 慢点 等一下
Aelita just be careful in the ice okay.
Aelita 在冰上要小心 好吗？
I'm worried.
我很担心
Okay mommy.
好的 妈妈
Let's get ready.
让我们准备好
I want to skate like mommy.
我想像妈妈一样滑冰
She's amazing.
她真了不起
Yeah she's very good with it indeed.
是的 事实上她非常擅长滑冰
whoo what can I do to skate like her?
喔 我怎么做才能像她那样滑冰呢
Well you have to train a lot and every day too.
恩 你必须经常训练 而且每天都要训练
Like with my piano lessons?
就像我的钢琴课一样？
Yes sweetheart like with the piano lessons.
是的 亲爱的 就像上钢琴课一样
[Music]
[音乐]
That was awesome darling.
那真是太棒了 亲爱的
Very well then.
很好 那么
gorgeous and perfect as usual.
华丽而完美 像往常一样
Thank you.
谢谢你
Now let's go home.
现在我们回家吧
Best day ever.
有史以来最好的一天
[Music]
[音乐]
Well if you like it so much, we can come here more often.
好吧 如果你这么喜欢的话 我们可以经常来这里
[Music]
[音乐]
Look at my giant snowball mommy.
看看我的大雪球妈妈
Stay near the house, sweetheart.
呆在房子附近 亲爱的
Well then my angel.
好吧 我的天使
What's that someone Waldo?
那是什么 Waldo？
I think it's a car.
我想是一辆车
[Music]
[音乐]
Mommy?
妈妈？
Waldo what's happening?
Waldo 发生什么事了？
Go protect Aelita.
去保护Aelita
Here they are.
他们来了
What should we do with them?
我们该怎么处理他们？
Get the woman.
抓住那个女人
What?
什么？
Over my dead body.
想都别想
Huh why not? Fine by me.
呵 吃我一拳
[Music]
[音乐]
No please. Waldo.
Waldo 求你了
Did you really think we wouldn't find out who's bought that old factory?
你真的认为我们不会发现是谁买了那个旧工厂吗？
We knew that you would attack project Carthage
我们知道你会攻击迦太基项目
and now we will pay with your life.
而现在我们就要用你的生命来偿还
Waldo.
Mommy.
妈妈
Daddy.
爸爸
Say goodbye to your family Waldo.
跟你的家人说再见吧 Waldo
Stop.
停下来
What? Why? I want to kill this traitor.
什么？为什么？我想杀了这个叛徒
He must suffer while he's alive.
他只有在活着的时候才会受苦
Death is an easy escape.
死亡是个容易逃脱的办法
Fine. don't forget this Franz.
好吧 别忘了这个 Franz
If you try to attack project Carthage again, you'll never see your daughter as well.
如果你再试图攻击迦太基项目 你也将见不到你的女儿
Come on. Let's not waste time.
来吧 让我们不要再浪费时间了
Enough chitchat. Let's go.
闲聊够了 我们走吧
Very well until next time, Waldo.
很好 后会有期 Waldo
[Music]
[音乐]
Mommy! Mommy!
妈妈 妈妈
Please, please, stop the car, Aelita!
求你了 求你了 把车停下来 Aelita
Aelita!
Aelita
Mommy!
妈妈